(Howard:)...and demands you take her right there,
right now, you'll just walk away?
(Leonard:)I said I'm her friend, not her gay friend.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey, I know you said
you didn't wanna talk...
(Sheldon:)- I don't.
- Okay, sorry.
(Leonard:)- Wait.
- Wait. Did you say wait?
(Penny:)Tell me the truth.
(Penny:)Am I just an idiot who picks giant losers?
(Leonard:)No, no.
(Penny:)Okay, so I pick good guys,
but turn them into losers?
(Leonard:)Of course not.
Well, it's gotta be one or the other.
Which is it?
(Leonard:)I'm sorry. What were the choices again?
(Penny:)I really thought Mike was different.
(Penny:)I thought he was sensitive and smart.
(Penny:)I mean, not you smart.
(Penny:)- Normal non-freaky smart.
- Yeah, no, sure.
(Penny:)You know, and then he just goes
and has to humiliate me...
(Penny:)...by writing about me on his blog
so the entire world can read it.